Metal Cardbot Commentary!
A Fire Truck Afraid of Fire!
Hello, friends! I'm Jun.
Let's watch the story of Metal Cardbot together!
It's "Metal Cardbot Commentary" time!
Phoenix Fire, Setup!
Hello, everyone!
My name is Phoenix Fire.
I am a brave rescue worker from Planet Machina.
Nice to meet you, Phoenix Fire!
Today, let's watch the story of
the brave rescue worker, Phoenix Fire!
Shall we get started?
Surprise!
Wow! This looks amazing!
You see? Everyone loves a little bit of a performance.
You really are the best, Dad!
Huh? Is there a fire?
It's getting closer...
Fire! Please evacuate!
Fire extinguished!
Phoenix Fire!
Why did you have to ruin the special gift I worked so hard to prepare for?
I'm sorry, Jun. I didn't realize...
If she liked the gift,
then maybe me and Anna could have...!
I-I'm not so sure about that. Hahaha!
Wha?? Cut it out, Phoenix Fire!
You can seal them, but you mustn't reveal the Metal Cardbots.
I know, but... urgh!
How do I set things straight with Anna then?
Phoenix Fire.
Huh? Do you know them, Mega Ambler?
Yes. We were part of the same rescue team.
He used to be the bravest firefighter.
Always jumping head first into the flames.
He received the Metal Medal, an honor awarded to only the best rescuers on planet Machina.
Wow, Phoenix Fire! You must've been a great rescue worker!
I was brave back then. The flames didn't bother me!
Heat couldn't hold you back, huh? In that case~!
Ow! Hot!
I'm not saying I couldn't feel the heat!
I- Where did he go? Jun! Get back here!
Jun, that's a smoke bomb! Don't touch it, it's not safe.
Oh! Okay...
Huh?
Is that another fire truck?
It's him!
Why does everyone break something when they show up?
This is great! Step on the gas and let's dance the night away!
I told you to stay still!
Theo! Are you okay?!
Ah, haha...
In my haste, I didn't realize...
You can't just break anything you'd like on Earth!
Blue Cop, use your Burst Shot!
Got it!
Burst Shot!
Huh? Fire...?
Augh!
That's...
That's Phoenix Fire's Metal Medal...
Fire! Everything will go up in flames if I don't stop this...
I'm sorry, Phoenix Fire. I didn't know you had such a painful experience.
It's okay, Jun.
Along with those memories, I also remembered my brave days as a rescue team member.
Really? Phew, that's a relief.
Ah! I almost forgot...
there's still some piping hot apple pie at home.
"Piping hot"?
I have to put it out, quickly!
P-Phoenix Fire! Are you okay?
Well, everyone? What did you think?
A fire truck afraid of fire. I finally succeeded in sealing Phoenix Fire!
Now then, look forward to the next "Metal Cardbot Commentary"!